|SENTENCE|俺と姉さんでは、呪いの性質が違う？​ 
Are the nature of the curse different between me and my sister?|TRANSLATION|Are the nature of the curse different between me and my sister?|END|
|SENTENCE|「いや、所長にもらったんだってさ」Yashiro|TRANSLATION|No, the director gave it to him.|END|
|SENTENCE|佳奈ちゃんに褒められまくり、さらにベルベットがうろたえる。|TRANSLATION|Kana is praised all over the place, and Velvet is even more woozy.|END|
|SENTENCE|ベルベットがうろたえ、俺に助けを求めるような視線を向ける。|TRANSLATION|Velvet scowls and looks to me for help.|END|
|SENTENCE|めっちゃ照れてる。肌が白いから、頬の紅潮が余計に目立つ。|TRANSLATION|She is extremely embarrassed, and the flush on her cheeks stands out even more because of her fair skin.|END|
|SENTENCE|「Yashiroくんが選んだの？」佳奈|TRANSLATION|Yashiro-kun chose it?|END|
|SENTENCE|うなずき、微笑む。​ 
I nod and smile.|TRANSLATION|I nod and smile. i nod and smile.|END|
|SENTENCE|「わ～、い～な～、かっわい～！私こういうの似合わないからな～。やばい、なでなでしたい」佳奈|TRANSLATION|I don't look good in this kind of thing. I want to stroke it.|END|
|SENTENCE|「」ベルベット|TRANSLATION|Velvet|END|
|SENTENCE|「ほら、似合うって言ったろ？」とニヤニヤしつつ視線を送ると、口をへの字にしてそっぽを向いてしまった。|TRANSLATION|When I looked at him with a grin and said, "See, I told you it would look good on you," he turned away with his mouth in a grimace.|END|
|SENTENCE|「あ、そう、これ！スコップ！」佳奈|TRANSLATION|Kana: "Oh, yes, here, a shovel!|END|
|SENTENCE|わかってる​ 
I know|TRANSLATION|I know. I know.|END|
|SENTENCE|迂闊にも、姉さんの前で眉をひそめてしまったのは引っかかることがあったから。​ 
The reason why I carelessly frowned in front of my sister was because I had gotten caught.|TRANSLATION|The reason why I carelessly frowned in front of my sister was because I had gotten caught.|END|
|SENTENCE|俺のことはいいから。大丈夫​ 
It's okay for me. Are you okay|TRANSLATION|It's okay for me Are you okay|END|
|SENTENCE|アヤコに呪われたせいで、俺は霊が見えるようになった。​ 
Because I was cursed by Ayako, I can now see spirits.|TRANSLATION|Because I was cursed by Ayako, I can now see spirits.|END|
|SENTENCE|確かあの世に半分引きずりこまれてしまったせいだ。​ 
I'm sure it's because I was half dragged into that world.|TRANSLATION|I'm sure it's because I was half dragged into that world.|END|
|SENTENCE|ごめんね～。　お姉ちゃんが元気なら、ちゃんと作ってあげられたのに～​ 
I'm sorry. If my sister was healthy, I could have made it for her.|TRANSLATION|I'm sorry. If my sister was healthy, I could have made it for her.|END|
|SENTENCE|姉さんがルリとルカの姿が見えないってことは、まだ俺よりもマシな状況、ってことか？​ 
Does the fact that you can't see Ruri and Ruka mean that your situation is still better than mine?|TRANSLATION|Does the fact that you can't see Ruri and Ruka mean that your situation is still better than mine?|END|
|SENTENCE|まだヤシロが赤ん坊だったころね​ 
When Yashiro was still a baby.|TRANSLATION|When Yashiro was still a baby.|END|
|SENTENCE|うん、ありがと～​ 
Yeah, thank you~|TRANSLATION|Yeah, thank you~ Yeah, thank you~|END|
|SENTENCE|けど、俺よりも明らかに症状が重いし。​ 
However, his symptoms are clearly more severe than mine.|TRANSLATION|However, his symptoms are clearly more severe than mine.|END|
|SENTENCE|ヤシロ？​ 
Yashiro?|TRANSLATION|Yashiro?|END|
|SENTENCE|あぁ、いや​ 
Oh, no|TRANSLATION|Oh, no. Oh, no.|END|
|SENTENCE|考えても、わかるはずないか。​ 
Even if you think about it, shouldn't you understand?|TRANSLATION|Even if you think about it, shouldn't you understand?|END|
|SENTENCE|そうだ、みかん持ってきたんだ。食べる？​ 
That's right, I brought some oranges. eat?|TRANSLATION|That's right, I brought some oranges.|END|
|SENTENCE|ん～あとで、いただこうかな​ 
Hmm, I guess I'll have it later.|TRANSLATION|Hmm, I guess I'll have it later.|END|
|SENTENCE|わかった。じゃあ、ここ置いておく​ 
Understood. Well, I'll leave it here.|TRANSLATION|Well, I'll leave it here.|END|
|SENTENCE|また謝る～​ 
Apologize again~|TRANSLATION|Apologize again~ Apologize again~.|END|
|SENTENCE|サイドボードにみかんを置き、姉さんのそばに戻る。​ 
I put the oranges on the sideboard and returned to my sister's side.|TRANSLATION|I put the oranges on the sideboard and returned to my sister's side.|END|
|SENTENCE|ご飯は？　ちゃんと食べた？​ 
What about rice? Did you eat properly?|TRANSLATION|What about rice? Did you eat properly?|END|
|SENTENCE|食べた。ちゃんと​ 
ate. properly|TRANSLATION|I ate. properly.|END|
|SENTENCE|ふふ、うん​ 
Hehe, yeah|TRANSLATION|Hehe, yeah|END|
|SENTENCE|ごめん、いつも心配かけて​ 
Sorry for always worrying you|TRANSLATION|Sorry for always worrying you|END|
|SENTENCE|負担もかけてる​ 
It's also a burden|TRANSLATION|It's also a burden|END|
